<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<gameofthrones>
   <Title>Images/Logo.png</Title>
   <TitleName>The Great Houses Of Westeros</TitleName>
   <Description>The great houses of Westeros are the primary players in the 
   political, economic, and military affairs of Westeros. There are eight great 
   houses in the land; Arryn, Baratheon, Greyjoy, Lannister, Stark, 
   Targaryen, Tully, and Tyrell. Each of these houses governs a specific region 
   and has the allegiance of many lesser houses.</Description>
   
   <houses id="1">
      
       <name>House Stark</name>
       <leader>Ned Stark(deceased)</leader>
       <Family>Catelyn Stark, Benjen Stark</Family>
       <BreifHistory>The Stark family traces its lineage back to the First Men, who 
           landed in Westeros more than 10,000 years ago and eventually forged a lasting 
           peace with the continent’s druidic natives, the Children of the Forest. The 
           Starks still worship the Old Gods of their forebears at the heart tree in 
           Winterfell.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Robb Stark</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>Winter Is Coming</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Bolton, House Cerwyn, House Hornwood, House Karstark, House Mormont, House Umber</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Baratheon and House Tully</Alliances>
                        
			   
			   <Enemy>House Lannister, House Greyjoy and House Taragaryen</Enemy>
		
   </houses>
   <houses id="2">
      
       <name>House Baratheon</name>
       <leader>Robert Baratheon(deceased)</leader>
       <Family>Cersei Baratheon, Stannis Baratheon and Renly Baratheon</Family>
       <BreifHistory>The House of Baratheon was founded after the conquest of Aegon 
           Targaryen by the conqueror's general (and rumored bastard brother) Orys Baratheon. 
           More recently, following Robert's Rebellion, the Baratheons of Storm's End seized 
           the Iron Throne from the Mad King Aerys Targaryen and have ruled the Seven 
           Kingdoms since.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Joffrey Baratheon</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>Ours Is the Fury</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Caron, House Swann</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Stark and House Lannister</Alliances>
                       
			   <Enemy>House Targaryen</Enemy>
			   
   </houses>
   <houses id="3">
      
       <name>House Lannister</name>
       <leader>Tywin Lannister</leader>
       <Family>Kevan Lannister, Dorna Lannister</Family>
       <BreifHistory>The Lannisters descend in part from a group of Andals who 
           invaded Westeros more than 6,000 years ago and settled at Casterly Rock. 
           The family ruled as kings in their realm until the Targaryens brought 
           dragons to conquer the continent, placing all the lords of Westeros under 
           control of the Iron Throne.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hier1>Ser Jaime Lannister</Hier1>
                 <Hier2>Tyrion Lannister</Hier2>
		 <TheirWords>Hear Me Roar</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Clegane, House CrakeHall, House Lefford, House Marbrand, House Swyft</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Baratheon and House Tyrell</Alliances>
			
			   
			   <Enemy>House Stark and House Tully</Enemy>
			   
			   
   </houses>
   <houses id="4">
      
       <name>House Tully</name>
       <leader>Hoster Tully</leader>
       <Family>Catelyn Tully and Lysa Tully</Family>
       <BreifHistory>The principal house of the Riverlands, the Tullys of Riverrun 
           rose to power during the Targaryen conquest. When the invaders attacked, 
           Edmyn Tully rebelled against the King of the Isles, Harren the Black, and 
           sided with Aegon Targaryen. Harren’s other supporters soon followed suit, 
           paving the way for the new king.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Edmure Tully</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>Family, Duty, Honor</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Blackwood, House Bracken, House Frey, House Mallister, House Whent</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Stark and House Arryn</Alliances>

			   
			   <Enemy>House Lannister</Enemy>
			   
   </houses>
   <houses>
      
       <name>House Arryn</name>
       <leader>Jon Arryn(deceased)</leader>
       <Family>Lysa Arryn, Alys Arryn(deceased) and Ronnel Arryn(deceased)</Family>
       <BreifHistory>Located in the Vale, the Arryns serve as wardens of the East 
           from their mountain stronghold, the Eyrie – a key defense against the violent
           clans that surround their home. According to lore, the Andal knight Ser 
           Artys Arryn took the Vale from the First Men, fighting from the back of a 
           giant falcon.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Robin Arryn</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>As High as Honor</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Baelish and House Royce</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Tully and House Stark</Alliances>
			
			
			   
			   <Enemy>House Lannister</Enemy>
			   
   </houses>
   <houses id="6">
      
       <name>House Targaryen</name>
       <leader>Daenerys Targaryen</leader>
       <Family>Viserys Taragaryen(deceased) and Khal Drogo(deceased)</Family>
       <BreifHistory>The Targaryens came from the ancient civilization of Valyria, 
           bringing dragons from the eastern continent and settling on the island of 
           Dragonstone. After an unknown disaster known as the Doom of Valyria wiped 
           out their homeland and killed most of the world’s dragons, the Targaryens 
           invaded Westeros.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>None</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>Fire and Blood</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>None</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>None</Alliances>
			
			
			   
			   <Enemy>All Great Houses of Westeros</Enemy>
			   
   </houses>
   <houses id="7">
      
       <name>House Tyrell</name>
       <leader>Mace Tyrell</leader>
       <Family>Olenna Tyrell, Alerie Tyrell and Margaery Tyrell</Family>
       <BreifHistory>For centuries, the Tyrells served and occasionally intermarried
           with House Gardener, the ancient family of the King of the Reach. But after 
           the Targaryen conquest eliminated the Gardeners, the Tyrells bent the knee 
           to the Iron Throne – and then rose to become principal house and warden of 
           the South at Highgarden.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Loras Tyrell</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>Growing Strong</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>House Redwyne</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>House Baratheon</Alliances>
			
			   
			   <Enemy>House Lannister, House Baratheon(of Storm's End) and House Martell </Enemy>
			
			   
   </houses>
   <houses id="8">
      
       <name>House Greyjoy</name>
       <leader>Balon Greyjoy</leader>
       <Family>Yara Greyjoy, Alannys Greyjoy, Rodrik Greyjoy and Maron Greyjoy</Family>
       <BreifHistory>House Greyjoy's power dates back to the great Grey King during 
           the Age of Heroes. Legend has it that the Grey King ruled the sea itself and 
           took a mermaid for his wife. After the Targaryen conquest, the people of the 
           Iron Islands chose the Greyjoys to serve as lords from Pyke.
       </BreifHistory>
         
		 <Hiers>Theon Greyjoy (Formally Thanks to Lord Bolton's Son)</Hiers>
		 <TheirWords>We Do Not Sow</TheirWords>
                 <SwornHouses>None</SwornHouses>
            
			<Alliances>None</Alliances>
			
			
			   
			   <Enemy>All Great House of Westeros</Enemy>
			   
   </houses>
   
   
</gameofthrones>