<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->


<gameofthrones>
    <Title>Images/Logo.png</Title>
    <EventName>The Red Wedding</EventName>
    <Involed>House Stark, House Tully, House Frey and House Lannister</Involed>
    <Death1>Robb Stark</Death1>
    <Death2>Catelyn Stark</Death2>
    <Death3>Talisa Stark</Death3>
    <Death4>The Northern Army</Death4>
    <Prelude>King Robb was lulled into a sense of security by Walder Frey 
        because he had extended Guest right to the Starks. 
        The betrayal was scheduled to occur after the formal ceremony and the 
        bedding, with Edmure and Roslin safely away in another part of the 
        castle to consummate their marriage.
        The door of the great hall is closed and barred by Black Walder. 
        Meanwhile, Roose Bolton and his men were to position themselves around 
        the hall, secretly armed and armored. The signal for massacre to begin 
        was for the musicians to play an instrumental version of The Rains of 
        Castamere.
    </Prelude>
    <Event>
        At Walder Frey's signal, Talisa is stabbed by Lame Lothar and the Northern 
        leadership with Robb Stark gathered 
        in the main hall is fired upon from the balcony by a group of assassins 
        armed with crossbows who were disguised as musicians during the wedding. 
        After the first volley the Northern guests are attacked in the main hall 
        by armed Frey and Bolton men.
        Meanwhile, Frey and Bolton men turn on the other Northern soldiers in the 
        camps who had been heavily drinking during the celebrations, taking them 
        completely by surprise.
        Robb, while wounded with several crossbow bolts, is still able to get back 
        onto his feet.
        At this point, Roose Bolton personally kills Robb by stabbing him through 
        the heart while saying "the Lannisters send their regards".Catelyn then 
        remains silent, staring at Robb's corpse in shock and utter despair, not 
        reacting as her own throat is slit from behind by Black Walder Frey.
    </Event>
    <Aftermath>Not only is Robb Stark himself killed in the betrayal, but the 
        entire Northern army that Robb Stark led to southern Westeros is also 
        destroyed - save only for those forces of House Karstark which had 
        earlier abandoned Robb to return home, and the forces of House Bolton 
        which turn on the other Northern Houses. Thus the Red Wedding ends 
        the conflict between House Stark and House Lannister in a decisive 
        victory for King Joffrey Baratheon and House Lannister. The War of 
        the Five Kings continues, however, as Balon Greyjoy still fights for 
        the Iron Islands' independence and Stannis Baratheon continues to 
        dispute Joffrey Baratheon's right to the Iron Throne.
    </Aftermath>
</gameofthrones>
